Now we are inside our wing IDE, and I'm just going to show you a few basic things to get started.
Firstly, in order to create a document you will click this icon up here.
And now this allows you to start writing some code.
If you want to close it or no longer need it, you click the X on the right hand side here and that
will close the document.
You can also use this icon to create multiple documents at once.
You'll see they're automatically saved as usually untitled and a number with coding.
Your name of your document is very important, so you want to save it as something that is meaningful,
which we'll cover later on.
So to save you just click file up here and we're going to choose save as in order to change the name.
Whenever you're saving make sure that when you change the name you don't also delete the dot p y.
If you do, then your document will no longer be able to run as a Python program, so you'll get an
error.
So let's call this.
And click save.
You now see it's changed up here on the top.
So that's a few basics about wing.
And as we go through the course you'll become quite an expert with using this IDE.